Now that you made your way through the material,
你已经学完了理论知识
you have a solid foundation in researching
并且充分掌握了交易策略研究基础知识
a trading strategy which will help you with finding an alpha signal.
这些策略可以帮助你寻找 alpha 信号
The next step on your journey is to do Project
接下来请完成实战项目 2
2 where you'll implement a breakout strategy.
在此项目中 你将实施一个突破策略
You'll take everything you learned from Project 1 to build this strategy,
你需要根据在实战项目 1 中学到的所有知识创建此策略
along with finding and filtering Outliers.
并且发现和滤除离群值
Transitions are really easy.
知识转换并不是那么简单
In transitioning from lessons to projects and back again,
有时候 纳米学位的学员会觉得
sometimes it's difficult for an entity students.
在课程知识与实战项目之间转换比较困难
That's true. I've gone through multiple Eudacity Nanodegree programs as a student,
没错我以学员身份学习了多个优达学城纳米学位课程
and I have to admit that starting a project was
我不得不承认
one of the loneliest parts of the process.
开始项目是最孤独的过程
I was a Eudacity student in the data analyst,
我学习了数据分析师
machine learning and deep learning Nanodegrees.
机器学习和深度学习纳米学位课程
Every time I started a new project, I struggled.
每次开始新的实战项目 我都觉得困难重重
I didn't really know if I would ever finish.
甚至不知道能否完成项目
Yeah.
是的
I would spend hours alone in the library just begging my code to magically work,
我在图书馆里一直琢磨着 渴望代码忽然能运行
and searching the web and online forums for hints.
并且在网上和论坛中搜索信息
So, there are definitely moments when I started to ask myself,
有时候 我不禁问自己
"What am I doing here?
“我这是何苦呢？
Why am I doing this to myself?"
干嘛要这么折磨自己啊”
That sounds really tough.
听起来很难
How did you handle those moments?
你是如何克服这些困难的？
Well, whenever I felt like I couldn't bring myself to keep trying,
每当我要泄气的时候
I would watch online guest speakers or interviews by
我就会看一些演讲或采访视频
people who did something really cool in the field that I was studying.
看看在相关领域取得瞩目成就的人是怎么说的
So, it helped to remind me why I was interested in the Nanodegree program to begin with,
看这些视频可以提醒我为何一开始要学习这门课程
and helped me to keep going forward.
并且激励我继续前行
Yeah. That's a really great idea.
是的这个方法很好
If you're ever feeling burnt out or tired from
如果你哪天泄气了
a day of debugging code or working on tough problems,
厌烦于一直调试代码或解决很难的问题
take a few seconds to remind yourself of
不妨花几秒钟思考下
what initially brought you to this Nanodegree program.
是什么促使你学习这门纳米学位课程的
What do you want to do? Who do you hope to become?
你想干什么？你想成为什么样的人才？
Watch some YouTube videos about this innovative field in which you're growing,
你可以观看一些关于这个领域的 YouTube 视频
maybe throw in a few cat and puppy videos along the way,
甚至还可以看几个小猫小狗的视频放松下
and when you feel that urge to move forward with your learning,
当你重新找到学习的动力后
dive back into your program.
再回来学习课程
Who knows where you'll go with your new skills and knowledge?
谁知道你会利用新的技能和知识创造出什么样的精彩成果呢